Right now,
your company is losing money.
Your company has a project.
It needs AI to get it done.
You want to send your data
to big AI like ChatGPT...
...but you can't. Your data is:
Private. Confidential. Classified.
So companies strip the names off the data
and send it anyway.
They think it's safe.
It's not.
This is the first problem we solved.
Stay with me.
Eighty-seven percent of people
can be re-identified from just
a zip code, a gender, and a birth date.
Anonymization is broken.
Your other details — age, location, diagnosis —
are enough to identify you.
Big data connects the dots.
But we sidestep this problem completely.
We invented a new way
to combine all your office computers
into one powerful AI.
Your data never leaves the building.
Sounds complicated? It's not.
Let me show you.
Bad way number one:
Imagine five workers, but only one brain.
One puts it on, does his job. Takes it off, passes it to the next.
Everyone else just stands there.
That's CrewAI, Swarms, LangGraph.
All their agents share one computer, one brain.
Only one thinks at a time. The rest wait.
Doesn't work.
Bad way number two:
Now each worker has his own brain,
but he works for a moment, stops, walks all the way
across the room to hand off his piece...
...walks all the way back, works a little more.
Most of the time — just walking.
That's Petals and Exo. They split one AI brain across computers. Each piece waits for the previous one.
The slow network between them
kills everything.
Doesn't work either.
The right way:
Distributed parallel AI.
Now imagine: before work begins,
every worker gets the complete plan.
Every worker has his own brain.
The whistle blows, and they ALL start
working at the same time.
Nobody stops.
Nobody walks anywhere.
Nobody waits for anyone.
Every computer gets its own complete AI
and its own piece of the project,
planned in advance.
They all think in parallel.
The project gets done
in a fraction of the time.
With BeehiveOfAI, we got the full power of AI —
and not one patient record left this hospital.
Our trade secrets
stayed inside our walls.
No leaks. No risk.
Every document stayed classified.
Full AI capability. Zero exposure.
Bob, you saved us a fortune.
We're running AI on our own computers now.
I'm promoting you to Head of Department.
Bobby, you're the reason
our data stayed safe.
I'm making you Senior Partner.
For your service to this country...
Colonel Bob,
your Hawaii vacation is approved.
Beehive of AI.
Not another multi-agent framework.
Actual distributed parallel AI.
This technology can also
make you money while you sleep —
with your own computer.
Check out our Public Mode video.
github dot com slash strulovitz.