Every night, your computer
is sitting there doing nothing.
It could be making you money.
You know how torrents work —
millions of small computers, together,
more powerful than any big server.
Now imagine the same thing, but for AI.
That's real. That exists.
And your computer can be part of it.
But unlike torrents, this is completely legal.
Here's why: companies need AI to get work done.
Big cloud AI is expensive.
Your computer, combined with thousands of others,
creates a cheap alternative. Companies are happy to pay for it.
That money goes to you.
There are other ways to earn from your computer.
Crypto mining. GPU rental. Bandwidth sharing.
They all run your hardware at full blast, 24/7.
Your electricity bill goes up. Your computer sounds like
a vacuum cleaner. Strangers run their code on your machine.
And after all that — you earn pennies.
Or maybe you've heard about AI agents
that trade stocks or run a business for you while you sleep.
In reality, most people lose money.
API costs run into thousands. The AI marks broken work as done.
And when it makes a mistake — legally, that's on you.
Not passive. Not safe.
We don't do any of that.
Your computer runs a small, free AI
that answers text questions. Light work. Low power.
No strangers' code. No money at risk.
Real companies pay for real work.
That money goes to you.
Imagine you're playing chess alone.
You need to find the best move.
You sit there, thinking through every possibility —
pawns, knights, bishops, rooks, queen.
One brain, so many options.
You can only think about so many moves
before your time runs out.
Now imagine you have six helpers.
You give each one a piece type.
You take pawns, you take knights, you take bishops.
Each helper goes to a separate room.
They all think at the same time.
Together, they explore far more possibilities
than you ever could alone.
Each one comes back with his best move.
You pick the winner. Next turn?
You show them all the new board, and they do it again.
Every turn, six brains. Every turn, a better move.
This works for any business problem.
Analyze two hundred customer reviews?
Split them across fifty computers.
Write fifty product descriptions?
Give each computer a different starting angle
— formal, playful, technical —
they all write at the same time.
And it scales effortlessly.
If your computer can play games, it can do this.
You install a free local AI — it's not an agent,
it doesn't take over your computer, it doesn't go online.
You ask it a text question, it gives back a text answer.
That's all it does. Our program is open-source —
you can read every line of code and see it's legit.
Install both, click start, walk away. Seventeen minutes.
When a customer pays for a job —
65% goes to the workers. That's you.
30% goes to the manager
who split and combined the work.
And the platform —
the website that connects everyone? Only 5%.
For comparison, Uber takes 25%. Apple takes 30%.
The platform takes 5.
Start as a worker tonight —
your laptop earns while you sleep.
Learn the system, become a manager —
the same software, bigger earnings,
30% of every job all to yourself.
Go even bigger — download the code,
run your own marketplace,
take 5% of every transaction.
Same technology. Three levels.
You choose how high you climb.
Every marketplace runs on the same
free, open-source code.
Don't trust one? Switch to another.
Or download the code and start your own.
Competition keeps every marketplace honest.
Nobody can overcharge you —
because anyone can compete with them tomorrow.
Sofia runs a small marketing agency.
A client needs two hundred customer reviews
analyzed by Friday.
She can't afford enterprise AI,
and she doesn't have time to read them herself.
She goes to a marketplace, submits the job,
sets her budget, and clicks submit.
Jade is a college student.
She installed the software
on her gaming laptop last week —
seventeen minutes.
Tonight, while she sleeps,
her laptop picks up task number forty-seven
from Sofia's job and gets to work.
Jade doesn't even know.
Marcus is a programmer by day.
On the side, he rents a cloud server
for a few dollars a month
and runs our software on it.
When Sofia's job arrives,
his server splits it into small tasks,
and sends one to each worker —
including Jade's laptop.
When all the workers finish,
Marcus's server collects the answers
and combines them into one polished report.
Marcus didn't lift a finger.
His cloud server did everything.
And that website where Sofia submitted her job?
Alex built it.
He downloaded the free open-source code,
set it up on his own domain,
and opened a marketplace.
Every transaction that flows through his platform,
he earns 5%.
The marketplace runs itself.
That report saved my client's product launch. They just signed a year-long contract.
My laptop paid for my textbooks this semester. I didn't do anything.
Last month, my hive earned me more than my side of the rent. My roommate thinks I'm a genius.
Alex started with free code
and a ten-dollar domain name.
His marketplace now handles
thousands of jobs a week.
Five percent of every transaction.
He's building the next eBay — of AI.
Your computer is going to sit idle again tonight.
Or it could start working for you.
The software is free.
The setup takes seventeen minutes.
Which step of the ladder will you reach?
This technology can also
get you promoted at work —
by saving your company a fortune.
Check out our Private Mode video.